[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Of what animal is the legendary Golden Fleece from Greek mythology?", "correct_answer": "Ram", "incorrect_answers": ["Cow", "Dragon", "Goat"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This is what they call a straight shot of absinthe served over a cube of sugar.", "correct_answer": "Van Gogh Crazy", "incorrect_answers": ["Traditional", "Short", "Neat"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the film The Crow, what was the name of the detective officer, with whom  Albrecht had repeated conflicts?", "correct_answer": "Torres", "incorrect_answers": ["Thompson", "Tandem", "Terrance"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Teleseisms are ground motions caused by a distant earthquake.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What country did the hot dog vendor in the movie Sleepers come from?", "correct_answer": "Greece", "incorrect_answers": ["Italy", "Ireland", "France"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In 1989, a Mastiff was recognized by the Guinness Book of World Records as the heaviest dog in the world. What was the weight of the dog?", "correct_answer": "343 pounds", "incorrect_answers": ["182 kilograms", "173 pounds", "298 pounds"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these Italian actors plays King Herod Antipas in The Passion of the Christ?", "correct_answer": "Luca De Dominicis", "incorrect_answers": ["Toni Bertorelli", "Emilio De Marchi", "Sergio Rubini"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "According to modern geological theories, there was only one continent about 200 million years ago. What do geologists call it?", "correct_answer": "Pangaea", "incorrect_answers": ["Panthalyssia", "Pannotia", "Rodinia"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the film 12 Angry men, this actor played Juror #3, an emotionally distraught father whose son hadnt spoken to him in two years.", "correct_answer": "Lee J. Cobb", "incorrect_answers": ["Martin Balsam", "E. G. Marshall", "Jack Klugman"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In Blackjack how is it accepted for a player holding the cards in his/her hand to give a sign to the dealer he/she wants to stand (stay)?", "correct_answer": "By sliding the cards under the bet", "incorrect_answers": ["By scraping the cards against the table", "None of these", "By placing additional chips next to the bet"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What defense tactic does the chinchilla use in order to escape from its predators, which include birds of prey, skunks, felines, snakes and canines?", "correct_answer": "Spraying urine", "incorrect_answers": ["Playing dead", "Squeaking", "Scratching"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "When Fred and Stacey meet in the movie Valley Girl, what does Fred say his favorite color is?", "correct_answer": "Magenta", "incorrect_answers": ["Fuchsia", "Melon", "Maroon"]}]